svsmarkets.com 2008-06-08

# SVS Markets > Privacy

In the privacy policy "SVS Markets", "we", "us" and "our" means City Index Limited and/or any of their affiliates that provide some or all of its products or services to you from time to time, and "you" means the individual who is using this website. If our Privacy policy changes, we will place an updated version on this page.

**Your Information**

**We define Your Information as personal information that:**

  1. is obtained from you or from third parties such as joint account holders, credit reference agencies (who may search the Electoral Register), fraud prevention agencies or other organisations when you apply for an account or any other product or service, or which you or they give to us at any other time; or
  2. relates to your account or is ascertained from the way you use and manage your account, from the transactions you make and from the payments which are made to your account. 

**You understand and agree to the following:**

  1. You authorise SVS Markets to use Your Information to perform credit and identity checks in relation to you at any time as it thinks fit including by asking for bankers’ references, by making enquiries of credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies, by searching the Electoral Register and by making any other enquiries we reasonably see fit. You understand that credit reference agencies will maintain a record of any enquiry made to them and the information given to them (and who may also use your details in the future to assist other organisations for credit purposes). SVS Markets may refuse to carry out an instruction or transaction for you as a result of any credit reference check. 
  2. SVS Markets shall be entitled to disclose your Information without prior reference to you (including as to late payments) to any regulator of SVS Markets business, to your employer if it is authorised or exempt under the FSMA 2000 (including its compliance officer and to send contract notes and statements of your account to that compliance officer), to credit reference agencies, fraud prevention agencies or to any other person SVS Markets reasonably believes to be seeking a reference or credit reference in good faith. In particular, SVS Markets shall be entitled to do so if you fail to make any payment when due, are in breach of the relevant product Terms and Policies, provide us with false or inaccurate information or if we suspect fraud. In addition you expressly agree: (a) that SVS Markets shall be entitled to inform an agent if SVS Markets accepts or rejects your application (and of the reasons for any rejection), (b) that SVS Markets shall be entitled to disclose details relating to your account to an agent and (c) that an agent is entitled to have access to all information relating to your account including information available on-line, trading information and account history.
  3. You agree that SVS Markets and/or its associated companies may store and process Your Information on their computers and in any other way. 
  4. You agree that SVS Markets and/or its associated companies will use Your Information to manage your account, provide statements and related services, for assessment and analysis (including market and product analysis) and to develop and improve our/their services.
  5. You agree that SVS Markets and/or its associated companies may provide Your Information to the following: 
    * anyone who provides a service to us or our associated companies or acts as our or our associated companies’ agent or sub-contractor (including in connection with legal proceedings), on the understanding that they will keep the information confidential
    * the persons referred to in clauses 1 and 2
    * anyone to whom we transfer all or any of our rights and/or obligations in relation to Your Information under the relevant product Terms and Policies and this privacy policy
    * any person to whom we have a duty to do so or to the extent that the law permits us to do so.
  6. SVS Markets and/or its associated companies will add your details to their respective databases/store information manually for the purposes of informing you (whether by letter, telephone (including text messages), electronically (by computer or otherwise) about products and services (including those of other persons) which may be of interest to you unless you tell us you do not wish to receive marketing material from SVS Markets and/or its associated companies by writing to us.
  7. For your protection and ours, to check instructions and to maintain high quality service standards, we may record and monitor calls made to or by us.
  8. Internet communications are not secure unless the data being sent is encrypted. We cannot accept any responsibility for unauthorised access by a third party or the corruption of data sent to or by us. For security, operational and business purposes we may monitor e-mails received by us or issued by us.
  9. We use a technology known as "cookies" as part of a normal business procedure to track patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. A cookie is an element of data that our website sends to your browser which is then stored on your system. We may store any information collected about you in this way which can be used to identify you when you visit our site in future, unless you change your browser settings to switch off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled
  10. You have the right at any time to request a copy of the personal data that we hold on you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to correct any inaccuracies. In order to maintain the accuracy of the data base, you can update your personal details by telephone.
  11. In order to process debit card transactions, the bank or card processing agency may require to verify your personal details for authorisation outside the EEA (European Economic Area). Therefore by browsing this website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of your personal information in this way. Save in the circumstances set out in clause five (d) of this policy, your information will not be transferred outside the EEA for any other purpose.
  12. If you have any questions about privacy please contact our Compliance Officer at: 

SVS Markets  
Moorgate Hall  
155 Moorgate  
London  
EC2M 6XB
